- How we can share data accross snowflake accounts
    - Sending data to another account
    - Sharing cloud services metadata with another account

- How to create a share
    - Create a share object
    - Add database objects to the share
    - Grant privileges on the share
    - Add accounts to the share
    - What is inbound and outbound shares
    - Can you grant all privileges on a share?

- How to consume a share
    - Create a database from the share
    - Query the shared data 

- Questions
    - Can you drop a table that is shared with another account?
    - Can you share a table that is shared with another account?
    - Can you clone a table that is imported as a share from another account?
    - Can you update/drop a table that is shared with another account?
    - Can a view be shared with another account?
      - What is a secure view? Why you cannot share a regular view with another account but a secure view can be shared?
      - How we can create a share with a secure view

- Reader accounts
    - What is a reader account?
    - For what use cases we can use reader accounts. What is the purpose of reader accounts?
    - How to create a reader account
    - How to share data with a reader account
    - Limitations of reader accounts
    - Can you create a share with a reader account?
    - What is the cost of using reader accounts? How it is billed or calculated?
    - When consumer open a reader account, does it need warehouse, roles, users, etc? Or it is automatically created by snowflake?
    - To create a reader account you also need to create share object? Why explain!
    - What limitations reader accounts have?
        - DML operations
        - Cloning
        - Time travel
        - Failover and replication
        - Data sharing


- Data sharing significance
    - What's the reason for data sharing?
    - What are the benefits of data sharing?
    - How data sharing can help in data collaboration and data monetization?
    - What are the use cases of data sharing in real world scenarios?